



jesusmarzor.vercel.app



blog-jesusmarzor.vercel.app



<u>/jesusmarzor</u>



<u>/jesusmarzor</u>



jesusmarzor28@gmail.com

Lenguages

Javacript Java PHP Python

Swift C++

Technologies

React Git

Docker Next.js Laravel Linux

MySQL **SCRUM**

Jesús Martín

Front-end Developer | iOS app Developer

Profile

I'm Jesús Martín Zorrilla, Computer Engineering.

I've studied web developer since 2021. I programme almost every day because it's one of my favorite hobbies.

I propose myself new objectives every day in order to continue learning and trying to use new technologies.

Experiences

iOS app Developer

august 2022 - Currently | Deloitte, Madrid

React Front-end Developer

february 2022 - august 2022 | Secrets-On, Madrid Responsabilities:

- I cooperated with the development of the website in wordpress.
- I cooperated with the development of the plataform.

Recommendations that I contributed:

- Work with a methodology agile.
- Use SASS and Suit CSS together.
- A folder structure more sustainable.

Stack: Wordpress, SASS, Suit CSS, Javascript, React, Docker.

Education

Degree in Computer Engineering - University of Granada september 2017 - july 2022

Cybersecurity course - HTL escuela de empresa online february 2022 - august 2022

Idiomas

Spanish | Native English | Basic